<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on TensorFlow for R</title><link>/installation/gpu/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on TensorFlow for R</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/installation/gpu/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cloud Desktop GPUs</title><link>/installation/gpu/cloud_desktop_gpu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installation/gpu/cloud_desktop_gpu/</guid><description>Overview Cloud desktops with various GPU configurations are available from Paperspace. With Paperspace, you can access a full Linux desktop running Ubuntu 16.04 all from within a web browser. An SSH interface is also available, as is a browser based RStudio Server interface (via SSH tunnel).
Paperspace offers an RStudio TensorFlow template with NVIDIA GPU libraries (CUDA 8.0 and cuDNN 6.0) pre-installed, along with the GPU version of TensorFlow v1.</description></item><item><title>Cloud Server GPUs</title><link>/installation/gpu/cloud_server_gpu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installation/gpu/cloud_server_gpu/</guid><description>Overview Cloud server instances with GPUs are available from services like Amazon EC2 and Google Compute Engine. You can use RStudio Server on these instances, making the development experience nearly identical to working locally.
Amazon EC2 RStudio has AWS Marketplace offerings that are designed to provide stable, secure, and high performance execution environments for deep learning applications running on Amazon EC2. The tensorflow, tfestimators, and keras R packages (along with their pre-requisites, including the GPU version of TensorFlow) are installed as part of the image.</description></item><item><title>Local GPU</title><link>/installation/gpu/local_gpu/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/installation/gpu/local_gpu/</guid><description>Overview TensorFlow can be configured to run on either CPUs or GPUs. The CPU version is much easier to install and configure so is the best starting place especially when you are first learning how to use TensorFlow. Here’s the guidance on CPU vs. GPU versions from the TensorFlow website:
TensorFlow with CPU support only. If your system does not have a NVIDIA® GPU, you must install this version.</description></item></channel></rss>