<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Overview on TensorFlow for R</title><link>/tools/</link><description>Recent content in Overview on TensorFlow for R</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/tools/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deploying Models</title><link>/tools/cloudml/deployment/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/cloudml/deployment/</guid><description>You can host your trained machine learning models in the cloud and use the Cloud ML prediction service to infer target values for new data. This page discusses model hosting and prediction and introduces considerations you should keep in mind for your projects.
Model Deployment Cloud ML Engine can host your models so that you can get predictions from them in the cloud. The process of hosting a saved model is called deployment.</description></item><item><title>Google Cloud Storage</title><link>/tools/cloudml/storage/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/cloudml/storage/</guid><description>Overview Google Cloud Storage is often used along with CloudML to manage and serve training data. This article provides details on:
Copying and synchronizing files between your local workstation and Google Cloud.
Reading data from Google Cloud Storage buckets from within a training script.
Varying data source configuration between local script development and CloudML training.
Copying Data Google Cloud Storage is organized around storage units named “buckets”, which are roughly analogous to filesystem directories.</description></item><item><title>Hyperparameter Tuning</title><link>/tools/cloudml/tuning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/cloudml/tuning/</guid><description>Overview This article describes hyperparameter tuning, which is the automated model enhancer provided by Cloud Machine Learning Engine. Hyperparameter tuning takes advantage of the processing infrastructure of Google Cloud Platform to test different hyperparameter configurations when training your model. It can give you optimized values for hyperparameters, which maximizes your model’s predictive accuracy.
What’s a hyperparameter? If you’re new to machine learning, you may have never encountered the term hyperparameters before.</description></item><item><title>Hyperparameter Tuning</title><link>/tools/tfruns/tuning/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/tfruns/tuning/</guid><description>Overview Tuning a model often requires exploring the impact of changes to many hyperparameters. The best way to approach this is generally not by changing the source code of the training script as we did above, but instead by defining flags for key parameters then training over the combinations of those flags to determine which combination of flags yields the best model.
Training Flags Here’s a declaration of 2 flags that control dropout rate within a model:</description></item><item><title>Managing Runs</title><link>/tools/tfruns/managing/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/tfruns/managing/</guid><description>Run Output Any graphical or console output as well as file artifacts created by a training run (e.g. saved models or saved model weights) can be viewed from the Output tab of the run view:
You can use the copy_run_files() function to export file artifacts from runs into another directory. For example:
copy_run_files(&#34;runs/2017-09-24T10-54-00Z&#34;, to = &#34;saved-model&#34;) You can also use the copy_run() function to export a run directory in it’s entirety.</description></item><item><title>R Interface to Google CloudML</title><link>/tools/cloudml/getting_started/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/cloudml/getting_started/</guid><description>Overview The cloudml package provides an R interface to Google Cloud Machine Learning Engine, a managed service that enables:
Scalable training of models built with the keras, tfestimators, and tensorflow R packages.
On-demand access to training on GPUs, including the new Tesla P100 GPUs from NVIDIA®.
Hyperparameter tuning to optmize key attributes of model architectures in order to maximize predictive accuracy.
Deployment of trained models to the Google global prediction platform that can support thousands of users and TBs of data.</description></item><item><title>TensorBoard</title><link>/tools/tensorboard/tensorboard/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/tensorboard/tensorboard/</guid><description>Overview The computations you’ll use TensorFlow for - like training a massive deep neural network - can be complex and confusing. To make it easier to understand, debug, and optimize TensorFlow programs, a suite of visualization tools called TensorBoard is available. You can use TensorBoard to visualize your TensorFlow graph, plot quantitative metrics about the execution of your graph, and show additional data like images that pass through it.</description></item><item><title>tfruns: Track and Visualize Training Runs</title><link>/tools/tfruns/overview/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/tfruns/overview/</guid><description>The tfruns package provides a suite of tools for tracking, visualizing, and managing TensorFlow training runs and experiments from R:
Track the hyperparameters, metrics, output, and source code of every training run.
Compare hyperparmaeters and metrics across runs to find the best performing model.
Automatically generate reports to visualize individual training runs or comparisons between runs.
No changes to source code required (run data is automatically captured for all Keras and TF Estimator models).</description></item><item><title>Training with CloudML</title><link>/tools/cloudml/training/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/tools/cloudml/training/</guid><description>Overview Training models with CloudML uses the following workflow:
Develop and test an R training script locally
Submit a job to CloudML to execute your script in the cloud
Monitor and collect the results of the job
Tune your model based on the results and repeat training as necessary
CloudML is a managed service where you pay only for the hardware resources that you use.</description></item></channel></rss>